geowarehouse.ca 2017-11-20

# GeoWarehouse Privacy Policy | GeoWarehouse

Contact our Privacy Officer with questions or comments:

**Privacy Officer**  
Address: 123 Front Street West, Suite 700.  
Toronto, ON  
M5J 2M2  
Telephone: 416-360-5263  
E-mail: PrivacyOfficer@teranet.ca

* * *

Your privacy is very important to us. Our privacy policy is to disclose to you what customer information we may gather and how we may use it, give you choice over what personal information we use for different purposes, other than statutory requirements, and provide access to the information we have in order to allow you to review or correct your information as appropriate. The policy that follows is our commitment to your privacy. We have adopted and subscribe to the privacy principles developed by the Canadian Standards Association. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our many offerings.

The range of products and services we offer continues to expand and the technology we use continues to change. But, no matter how our business changes, we will always do our best to protect your privacy. This policy will be reviewed for appropriateness from time to time as our users and requirements change. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.

**1\. What Information We Collect:**

Like most organizations, we collect and use personal information about our customers and visitors to our web sites. Personal information means any information about an identifiable individual. We collect your personal information online to provide you with the most personalized web experience possible. In many cases the more we know about you the more value we can offer you.

Personal information will only be collected by fair and lawful means. Our collection of personal information will be limited to that necessary for the purposes we have identified to you. By providing us with your personal information and using our site, you are deemed to have provided your permission to this collection and use of information for the purposes set out herein.

Information collected may include: contact information such as your name, company name, address, billing address, phone/fax numbers, e-mail address; billing information such as credit card information or bank account information, tracking information from cheques and money orders; client docket information; areas of practice; and details regarding your business transactions with us.

**2\. How We Use the Information We Collect:**

We collect information throughout our web site, including statistics, domain names and/or IP addresses to help diagnose technical problems, administer our web site and to provide you with information on products or services that might be of interest to you. We retain the content of e-mails that you send us, your e-mail address and our responses in order to handle any follow-up questions you may have.

We use the contact information and areas of interest information, as appropriate, in the normal course of our business to build your account with us, send you requested information, provide you with our products or services, personalize the delivery of site content to you or contact you when necessary. Personal information is required in order to identify you as a customer and to provide you with access to our products and services and other products and services we feel might be of interest to you. Billing information and client docket information that is collected is used to bill you for products and services that you request.

In order to provide you with our best service, it may be necessary for us and our affiliated companies, to share the personal information you have provided, with each other. Also, this site has several necessary content suppliers who assist in providing the services or products associated with this site. As part of the operations of the site, these companies may have access to your personal information. In particular, we will provide personal information to third party suppliers so they can fulfill any orders you may place through the shopping cart.

Aggregate data:

We may also use personal information and data collected to generate statistics and aggregate reports for internal use, such as new product development and marketing and for sharing with affiliates, subsidiaries, licensees, content suppliers, successors and advertisers. These statistics and aggregate reports will not contain any personally identifiable information; your identity is kept anonymous.

Cookies:

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer’s hard drive for record keeping purposes. Our use of cookies allows you to enter your password less frequently and allows us to personalize your online interaction with us by alerting you to information, products or services we think would be of interest to you. The use of cookies is an industry standard and many major web sites use them to provide useful features to their customers. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user’s computer. With most Internet browsers you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is used. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.

Limiting the Use of Information:

We will not use personal information for purposes other than: those for which it is collected; for legitimate practices; or for uses consistent with previous uses or with specified purposes, except with your consent or as required by law. We will retain personal information only as long as is necessary for the fulfillment of the purposes for which it was collected or as a requirement for government and/or registration purposes. Further we will not use or share the personal information provided to us in ways unrelated to the purposes for which it was collected or to legitimate practices or to consistent uses, without also providing you with an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. You may withdraw your permission at any time after you have given it, provided that there are no contractual restrictions or legal requirements to prevent this.

From time to time, we will notify users of new products, services, partnerships and upgrades. If you currently receive updates and wish to opt-out, you can send an e-mail to info@teranet.ca with remove me in the subject line.

Disclosing Information Collected:

We may disclose personal information without your consent where such disclosure is: required by law, regulation or government request; required to comply with a warrant or court order; related to an offence that has been or is about to be committed; required due to an emergency; made for the purpose of collecting a debt owed by you; made to our lawyers or other agents in the course of representing us; protecting our rights or property and that of our users, sponsors, providers, licensors or merchants; or necessary or appropriate to site operation.

Business Transfers:

As we continue to develop our business, we may acquire additional companies. In such transactions, customer information is generally one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that Teranet or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the transferred assets.

Safeguarding Information:

We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We have adopted appropriate safeguards to ensure that personal information is secure against disclosure, loss or theft or unauthorized access, copying, use or modification. Such safeguards include physical measures, such as restricting access to offices and filing cabinets, organizational measures, such as limiting access to personal information on a need to know basis and technological measures such as using passwords and encryption. Our employees are aware of the importance of maintaining the confidentiality of personal information. Please see our Security Statement.

As the Internet is not a totally secure medium, we cannot guarantee that our safeguards will always be totally effective particularly in cases of fraudulent conduct or fraudulent concealment, provision by third parties of incorrect data, willful actions by third parties to corrupt or tamper with the database and/or the data and other such actions or occurrences.

Links To Other Sites:

We would like to remind you that we provide additional links to resources we believe may be useful to you. These links will lead you to sites operated by different organizations with different privacy practices. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. **3\. How to Contact Us:**

Upon request and reasonable notice customers will be given information about their personal information held by us. You will be provided with an opportunity to confirm the accuracy and completeness of your personal information and have it amended. Please see our Access to Personal Information Policy.

* * *

**Accessing your Personal Information**

You may access and verify your personal information. Upon receipt of a written request you will be informed, within a reasonable time following such request, of the existence, use and disclosure of your personal information. In order to safeguard personal information we may need specific identification information from you in order to verify your identify before we can provide you with the personal information we hold.

There may be instances when we will not be able to provide you with the personal information that you request, for instance if your personal information: contains references to other persons, has already been destroyed due to legal requirements or because we no longer needed it for our purposes, is subject to legal privilege, contains confidential proprietary information, or cannot be disclosed for other legal reasons.

In instances that we are unable to provide you with access to your personal information you will be informed of the reasons why access has been denied, except where we are prohibited from doing so by law.

To help us provide you with the personal information that you are seeking please be as specific as possible in describing the records you want to access. You should provide your full name, and any other names that you have previously used, and any identifying number that relates to the records, such as account number, file number or other reference number you may have received. If you are requesting records for another person, you must provide proof that you have authority to act for that person. Also you should enter the time period for the requested records (for example, ‘October 2003 to present’).

There is no cost for reasonable requests for access to your personal information, but there may be a fee to retrieve and supply you with copies of records. We will advise you of the fee, if any, prior to providing your information.

**Correcting your Personal Information**

We are committed to maintaining the accuracy of your personal information for as long as it is being used for the purposes we have identified to you, and provided that you keep us up-to-date. Having accurate information about you enables us to give you the best possible service. To help us keep your personal information current, we encourage you to notify us of inaccuracies or corrections or changes such as a new address or change of telephone number. We may ask you to put your request for a correction in writing and may ask you to verify your identity.
